const DATA = [
    {
        question: 'Who gets pushed off of the tower in Winterfell?',
        answers: [
            'Rob',
            'Arya',
            'John',
            'Bran'],
        correctAnswer: 'Bran'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who has a direwolf named Nymeria?',
        answers: [
            'Rob',
            'John',
            'Sansa',
            'Arya'],
        correctAnswer: 'Arya'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who said “Chaos isn’t a pit. Chaos is a ladder.”?',
        answers: [
             'Varys',
             'Petyr Baelish',
             'Bronn',
             'Daario Naharis'],
        correctAnswer: 'Petyr Baelish'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who trained Arya how to use a sword?',
        answers: [
             'Eddard Stark',
             'John Snow',
             'Jaqen H’ghar',
             'Syrio Forel'],
        correctAnswer: 'Syrio Forel' 
    },
    {
        question: 'How many dragons does Daenarys have?',
        answers: [
            'One',
            'Three',
            'Four',
            'None'],
        correctAnswer: 'Three'  
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of John Snow’s sword?',
        answers: [
            'Ice',
            'Needle',
            'Oathkeeper',
            'Longclaw'],
        correctAnswer: 'Longclaw'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is John Snows real name?',
        answers: [
            'Rhaeghar', 
            'Viserys',
            'Drogo',
            'Aegon'],
        correctAnswer: 'Aegon'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'Who is Robert Baratheon\'s blood son',
        answers: [
            'Podrick',
            'Tommen',
            'Gendry', 
            'Rickon'],
        correctAnswer: 'Gendry'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where is Winterfell located?',
        answers: [
            'South',
            'East',
            'North',
            'West'],
        correctAnswer: 'North'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who created the Night King?',
        answers: [
            'The Lanisters',
            'The First Men',
            'The Mad King',
            'The Children of The Forest'],
        correctAnswer: 'The Children of The Forest',    
        
    }
];